Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Issues, 1930-2004; 1; 58.4 cubic ft.
  - Hazardous Waste, 1972-1995; 1.6; 8.0 cubic ft.
    - Statute of Limitation, Bills, Memos, and Fact Sheets, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Statute of Limitations, Bills, Memos, and Fact Sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Statute of Limitations, General Information, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Statute of Limitations, General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Statute of Limitations, News Clippings, 1981-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Strict Liability, 1983-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Subcommittee on Hazardous Waste, Undated (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Superfund, 1983-1991 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Superfund, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Superfund, Assembly Hearing, Hempstead, New York, 1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Superfund, Clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Superfund, Management Board, 1983-1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Superfund, New York State, 1982-1983 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Superfund, New York State, 1984-1987 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Superfund, New York State Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Superfund, Other States, 1980-1983 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Superlien, 1981-1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Testimony and Reports, 1984; 1988 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Testimony, Superfund Management Board, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Toxics, Asbestos, 1978-1983 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Superfund Enforcement Performance, 1990 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Toxics, Asbestos, 1984-1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Toxics, Asbestos, Reports, 1985-1991 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Toxics, Cancer and Health, 1975-1981 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Toxics, Cancer and Health, 1982-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Toxics, Chemical Release, Clippings, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Toxics, Chemical Release, General Information, 1975-1982 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Toxics, Chemical Release, General Information, 1983-1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Toxics, Chemical Release, General Information, 1985-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Toxics, Chemical Release, Legislation, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Toxics, Chemical Releases, Reports, 1983-1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Toxics, Clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Toxics, Community Right to Know, 1979; 1983-1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Toxics, Crimes, 1984-1985 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Toxics, Crimes, 1986-1988 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Toxics, Dioxins, 1979; 1981-1984 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Toxics, Dioxins, 1985-1987 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Toxics, Enforcement, 1983-1985 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Toxics, Federal Regulations (not RCRA or TSCA), 1979-1983 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Toxics, Chlorine, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Toxics, Chemical Sensitivity, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Toxics, Breast Cancer and the Environment: The Chlorine Connection, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Toxics, Fairways, 1994 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Toxics, Local Solutions to Toxic Pollution, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Toxics, Financial Assurance Testimony, 1982 April 20 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Toxic Fires, 1982-1985 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Toxics In Your Community, 1984; 1986 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Toxics, Methylcyclopentadienyl Manganese Tricarbonyl (MMT), 1985; 1993-1994 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Toxic Pollutants, 1990-1992 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Toxic Pollution, 1983; 1988-1989 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Toxic Substance Control Act, 1983-1986 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Toxics, Underground Storage Tanks, 1987-1989 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, Undated (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Transportation of, 1981; 1986-1987 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Underground Petroleum Storage, Legislation, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Underground Petroleum Storage, Reports, I, 1990-1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Underground Petroleum Storage, Reports, II, 1988-1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Waste Disposal, General, 1979-1983 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Waste Disposal, General, 1984-1989 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Waste Oil, 1982-1985 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Workers Right to Know, 1979-1985 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Protections for New York State, Volume 1, 1994 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Protections for New York State, Volume 2, 1994 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1992 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Cortland County Lowe Level Radioactive Waste Office, Press Release, 1994 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Developmental and Reproductive Toxicology: Studies and Test Systems and Publications, 1990 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Toxic Chemical Accidents in New York State, 1985-1990 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Cancer Incidence by County, Volume I, 1982 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Cancer Incidence by County, Volume II, 1982 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Cancer Facts and Figures, 1991 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Environmental Pollution Cases Deep Concern, 1985 (Box 8 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
  - Land Use, 1967-2000; 1.7; 2.0 cubic ft.
    The subseries Land Use contains bills, correspondence, memorandums, news clippings, reports, and legislation related to floodplain management, farm use, open space, and sustainable agriculture.
    - Acquisition Bill, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Legislation, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, Reports, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Agriculture, Testimony, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Anti-speculation Bill, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Conserving Open Space in New York State, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Dolan, Farm Protection, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Farmland Preservation, 1989; 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Farmland Preservation, 1979-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Farmland Preservation, 1988-2000 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Floodplain Management, 1975-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - General Information, 1974-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - General Information, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Greenbelt, 1981-1983; 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Hudson River Valley Greenway, 1988-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Land Acquisition, General Information and Reports, 1986-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Land Acquisition, Memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Land Acquisition, Notes and News Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Land Management, Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Land Trusts, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Land Use Law Reporter, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Land Use, Transportation and Air Quality, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Microwave Towers, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Minnesota, 1982; 1990; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - New York State Law, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Noise, General Information, 1975-1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Open Space, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Open Space, Legislation, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Open Space, Towers and Traffic, 1985-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Other States, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Pace University, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Pesticides, 1985-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Pine Barrens, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Planning, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Plans, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Preservation, 1988-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Property Tax Exemption, 1979; 1987-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Real Estate Transfer Tax, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Reform, Reports, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 1974; 1980; 1982 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Tower Bills, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Transfer of Development Rights, 1978; 1980-1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Transportation Planning, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Yard Use, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Toward a Long-Term Strategy for Farmland Protection and Soil and Water Conservation in New York, 2000 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Albany Urban Cultural Park, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Agriculture and the Environment: A Convergence of Interest, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Community Planning: Plans and Projects, Undated (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Land Use Planning for the Adirondack Park, Undated (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - A North Cascades National Park for America's Alps, 1967 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
  - Lead, 1987-1994; 1.8; 3.0 cubic ft.
    The Lead subseries includes correspondence, fact sheets, conference proceedings, and reports related to the Coalition for a Lead Free New York, Lead Alliance conference, and lead poisoning.
    - Abatement, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Abatement Training Course, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Advisory Council, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Background Information, Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Bronx Legal Services, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - California Industry Tax for Lead, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Childhood Lead Poisoning, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Coalition for a Lead Free New York, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Coalition for a Lead Free New York, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Coalition for a Lead Free New York, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Coalition for a Lead Free New York, Directory, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Coalition for a Lead Free New York, Membership List, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Commercial Insurance, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - County Screening, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Department of Health, Draft Screening Ruler, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Department of Health, Part 67-Z, Lead Regulations, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Drinking Water, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Fact Sheets, 1989-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Federal Testimony, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Figurines, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Forum, Albany, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Forum, Binghamton, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Forum, Buffalo, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Forum, Long Island, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Get the Lead Out, New York Public Interest Research Group Handbook for Lead Poisoning Prevention, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Grant Foundations and Proposals, 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Hearing, Brooklyn, NY, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Housing and Urban Development Money, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Insurance Testimony, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Lead Alliance Conference, 1991; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Lead Alliance Conference, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Lead Alliance Conference, 1994 Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Lead Alliance Conference, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Lead Alliance Conference, Notebook, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Lead Based Paint Hazard Control Grant Program, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Lead Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Lead Poisoning, 1988; 1992-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Lead Poisoning, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Lead Poisoning, New York Laws, Bills, EPL/Coalition Efforts, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Lead Poisoning, Other States, Legislation, Resources, Law, 1987-1988; 1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Lead Poisoning, Scientific Studies and Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Lead Poisoning, Scientific Studies and Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Lead Poisoning, Scientific Studies and Reports, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Lead Poisoning Conference, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Lead Poisoning Prevention Action Plan, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Lead Poisoning Prevention Coalition, Correspondence from Other Organizations, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Lead Pumps, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Legislation, 1987-1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Lobbying File, 1985-1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Lobbying File (A.11670/S.8559), 1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984; 1986; 1990-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - New York State Lead Poisoning Prevention Advisory Council, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - New York State Lead Poisoning Prevention Advisory Council, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - New York State Legislative Committee on Toxic Substances Hearings, Lead Abatement Worker Training, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Notes and Clippings, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Playgrounds, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Press Conference, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Reports, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1990-1991; 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Report, "The Public Health Issue of the 1990's: The Lead Hazard", 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Report, "The Public Health Issue of the 1990's: The Lead Hazard", 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Robert Sterling Clark, Grant, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Safe Houses, 1994 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Testimony, 1990-1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Worker Training Legislation, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Resource Guide for Lead-Based Paint Clean-Up, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - A Technical Manual on Lead, 1994 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Legislation, Lead, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Legislation, Lead, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Legislation, Lead, 1992 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Legislation, Lead, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Legislation, Lead, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Ban on Lead-Soldered Cans, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-2004; 1.9; 4.0 cubic ft.
    The Miscellaneous subseries is primarily composed of legislative activity collected weekly by Environmental Advocates. Also of interest in this subseries is the material related to Citizen Suits.
    - Assembly Hearing, "The Future of Environmental Programs in New York State", 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Assembly Hearing, "Regulatory Reform/Continuing Departmental Oversight", 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Campaign Contributions, Legislative, 1982-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Cancer, Reports and Statistics, 1985-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Casino Gambling, General Information, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Citizen Suits, 1991 Coalition, Letters from Coalition Members, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Citizen Suits, 1991 Coalition, Miscellaneous Material, 1987-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Citizen Suits, 1991 Coalition, Reply Forms (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Citizen Suits, 1991 Coalition, Reply Forms, Legislation (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Citizen Suits, Articles for Newsletter, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Citizen Suits, Bills and Historical, 1974-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Citizen Suits, General Information, 1973-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Citizen Suits, General Information, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Citizen Suits, General Information, 1988-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Citizen Suits, Legislation, Bills, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Citizen Suits, Legislation, Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Citizen Suits, Legislation, Fact Sheet, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Citizen Suits, Legislation, Memoranda, 1985-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Citizen Suits, Other States, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Citizen Suits, Pedone Demolition Site, 1985-1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Citizen Suits, Reports, 1988; 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Citizens Protection Act Legislation, 1975-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Citizens Protection Act Legislation, Including Other States, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Conservation Corps, General Information, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Conservation Easements, Easement Legislation, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Conservation Easements, Easement Legislation, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Conservation Easements, General Information, 1976-1979; 1982-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Cost Benefit Analysis, Department of Environmental Conservation, Department of Health Meeting, 1995 October 03 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Cost Benefit Analysis, GORR Regulations, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Cost Benefit Analysis, Risk Assessment, 1992; 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Annual Reports, 1974; 1984-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Environmental Board, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Environmental Management Councils, 1973; 1982-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Emergency Permits, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, General Information, 1981-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Legislative Proposals, 1981-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Miscellaneous Legislation, 1985-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, News Clippings, 1983-1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, News Releases, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Department of Environmental Conservation, Uniform Procedures Testimony, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Department of Health, Environmental Health, 1978; 1982-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Department of Health, Health Monitoring at Superfund Sites, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Dole/Johnson Regulatory Reform, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Environmental Economics, General Information, 1980-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Environmental Health, 1988-1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Environmental Regulation and Reform (S.3683), 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Global Warming, Bills and Fact Sheet, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Governor George E. Pataki: Environmental Protection Transition Committee, Draft Proposals, 1994 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Health Surveys, General Information, 1985-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Health Surveys, Medical Monitoring, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Historic Preservation, General Information, 1984-1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Historic Preservation League, 1978-1979; 1983-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Insurance, 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Insurance, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Insurance, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)